I said get out here!
Don't tell me you lost your swagger this easily!
Come on, you pig!
You've had this coming.
Ah!
I told you again and again what would happen.
Yet you still betray me.
Shishi!
Damn you all!
No!
Oh!
No!!
I'm fine.
I'm fine. You barely cursed me.
Stay back, Lugwali. You're still injured.
Idiot. You're the one with the bullet wound.
It hurts so much. I'm scared. And I miss...
I'm scared.
Oh!
L거광
This is over now.
Shenzhen!
Just go!
Run!
Stop right there!
Hey, Xiao Li.
Of all our former colleagues I've killed so far, which one was your favorite?
You bastard! I'm bringing you in!
You're done! Just give up!
Just give up!
No!
If marriage counseling isn't working, then I hate to say it, but...
it might be time to look for an attorney.
Well, I've given it some thought.
It would get me away from him.
But after that, I can't support the kids.
Not with all of Shishi's issues.
What can I do to help?
That's kind of you.
But I don't want to impose.
Ah...
Shishi?
You're awake.
Why are you crying?
Was it a nightmare?
Don't do it!
If you leave Dad, then we can't be a family!
I...
I told you to stop eating my mommy!
Had enough?
Huh?
What?
That was your last god damn mistake?
You...
Earthless piece of trash.
I tried to give you a chance.
But now you've gone past the point of forgiveness.
UGH!
Ugh!
I'm gonna remind you...
That you're mine.
Huh?
No, wait!
Mom isn't strong enough to fight back, so I'll do it for her.
You're a psycho! A goddamn psycho!
Yeah!
It's alright, Mom. We took care of him.
Come on.
Hello.
It's so wild saying hi to you like this.
Kind of a trip.
The man's got a baby on the way.
What a shame.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Why can't I control myself?
My love.
I'm sorry.
I should've been better to you.
I didn't always know how to protect you too.
I'm so sorry!
My loves. I'm so sorry.
I should've been better to you.
I didn't always know how to protect you two.
I tried my best for so long.
I loved you.
But in the end, I only made things worse.
Don't do it!
If you leave Dad, then we can't be a family!
I told you to stop me and my mommy!
Oh, Xixi.
I'm sorry.
I'm not leaving your father.
And I'm not leaving you.
But you have to promise me
you'll never talk about what you heard today, alright?
How could that happen?
Xixi!
Dad, you sure we're going the right way?
Of course I'm sure.
We could find someone to ask.
Excuse me!
Hands off!
Your friend might want these.
Oh, one thing.
Do you know where the special needs building is?
Oh, that was the wrong way.
Now, now.
I see you taught Xixi some new science.
What did she say?
She says I'm a good brother.
All right, then.
What brings you in?
About six months ago, she suddenly lost her voice.
We've seen all kinds of doctors, but no answers yet.
Do you know when she'll be back?
This is the Mental Health Center.
And we wanted to follow up about making a counseling appointment.
You're safe.
I'm here.
Hey, Mom.
Do the siblings in your story ever find their way back home?
...
Chao Ling!
Wake up!
Mr. Liu, here!
Yes, mom. We just left.
Well, it's been years. A lot has changed.
Yes, your brother's death was certainly a sudden one.
He would have been excited to see you.
Let's not talk about this anymore. What time should I expect you home?
Later. I have plans.
Huh? Can't they wait?
It's been long enough.
You see?
I said we'd meet again.
Why did you share your memories?
Did you even mean to?
Were you wanting to share all those secrets you'd seen?
Even?
Will you help us?
We're trying to find our friend.
Please look. I know what you can do.
So use this to see where he is.
Even Liu Kuang's memories.
Well, here it is.
Liu means phone.
Hmph.
And you?
What's next?
Do I have a choice?
Oh, yes.
More than one.
You see, fate is comprised of many parallel lines.
It can be driven by personality.
As well, as the actions of others.
Sometimes we change the line we're on.
Sometimes we can't.
Damn you all!
No!
How is it possible?
Did he actually see Cheng Xiaoshi die?
A guest has arrived.
Maybe I'm overthinking it.
Hey, took it easy.
Yeah, yeah.
Finally, Hong Sweet Home.
I'll cut the act.
Come on.
Let me have this.
My two favorite tenants are back.
We've been in the hospital for two months.
Zhang Xiaoshi, could you please read the room?
What do you mean?
What?
Yeah, that's more like it.
Thanks, favorite landlady.
Well, Lu Guang, you know what to do.
Come here.
Huh?
Wait, Lu Guang?
Not cool.
Seriously?
Dude, I got shot.
The least you can do is help me over to where I can stuff my face.
Captain, how's Officer Wang?
Finally out of the woods, but she still has a while before she's recovered.
Plus, for future paranormal stuff, there's a new force, and I'm in charge.
I want to bring lines together.
Make the uncertain, certain.
Mm-hmm.
Can you do that?
I think it depends.
We're still friends, right?
You forgot something.
I don't need it.
That hits the spot.
Especially after hospital food.
Hmm.
Hey, why aren't you eating?
Zhang Xiaoxian.
I'm sorry.
I'm always telling you to leave the past untouched.
But I couldn't follow my own words.
Even if I know that death is an unchangeable point,
I still want to use the last chance
to go back to the beginning.
And save you.
Oh, my God.
Teacher, I'll show you.